Guide to the Ken Kennedy academic records, 1967-2007 MS 206
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: Centers, 1988-2007 (Boxes 1-16)
  - Subseries C: Gulf Coast Center for Computational Research (GC4R), 2002-2006
    - Apple Workgroup Cluster for Bioinformatics (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - GC4R Bi-weekly Ed. Init. Teleconferences 2004 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - GCC/Keck Annual Report 2004 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - NCBC (KK's copy) (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - NCI/NIH RFA-CA-04-013 Interactive Cancer Biology (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - NSF: ITR 04-012 Automatic Generation of High-Performance Domain Languages (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - CCC Pre-proposal Draft with Bradley and Marek (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Meeting with Dr. Levy re: Computational Cancer Center 2003 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Computational Cancer Center Meeting 2003 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Meeting with Don Berry re: CCC 2003 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Ross and Margot Perot Center for Computational Cancer Research Proposal 2002 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - NCI caBIG Meeting (GCC). 25 August 2003 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - NCBC Proposal Development Meeting. 25 November 2003 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - NCBC Proposal -draft announcement cancelling. December 2003 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - NCBC Proposal Meetings. 21 January 2003 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Moshe's Meeting with Don Berry and Dr. Gillis re: CCC. October 2003 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - NCBC Meeting with UTHSC. 12 Dec 2003 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Meeting with Tony E. re: NCBC. 8 Dec 2003 (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - NCBC Proposal Meeting. 6 Dec 2003 (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - NCBC Weekly Proposal Meeting. Dec 2003 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - NCBC Status - Lunch Meetings with Tony Elam (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - GCC Interdisciplinary Network Meeting. 28 January 2005 (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - GC4R Talk at Rice. Dr. Guerrero. 14 January 2005 (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - MDACC/GC4R Talk Lydia Kavraki at MDACC. 7 September 2004 (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - GC4R Press Release Draft December 2003 (Box 16, Folder 62)
    - Comp. Cancer Center Meeting Handouts. 23 July 2003 (Box 16, Folder 63)
    - Gulf Coast Center for Computational Cancer Rice and MDACC. October 2003 (Box 16, Folder 64)
    - Meeting with Apple re: GC4R. 10 August 2004 (Box 16, Folder 65)
    - Computational Cancer Center - Planning Meeting. 7 February 2003 (Box 16, Folder 66)
    - GC4R Event at Rice. 19 March 2004 (Box 16, Folder 67)
    - GC4R Event at MDACC (Devika's Talk). 6 February 2004 (Box 16, Folder 68)
    - Planning Meeting for GC4R at MDACC. 23 January 2004 (Box 16, Folder 69)
    - GC4R Kick off Meeting. 5 December 2003 (Box 16, Folder 70)
    - Ken Kennedy Seminar at MDACC. 25 October 2002 (Box 16, Folder 71)
    - Computational Cancer Center Meeting. 17 June 2003 (Box 16, Folder 72)
    - GCCB Meeting at Rice. 3 January 2003 (Box 16, Folder 73)
    - Meeting with Richard Gibbs, Baylor HGC. 14 January 2004 (Box 16, Folder 74)
    - Bioinformatics Workshop. December 2003 (Box 16, Folder 75)
    - Compiler Group Meeting with Paul Havlak/Genome Assembly. 23 January 2004 (Box 16, Folder 76)
    - Ken Calls Dr. Wah Chiu. 2 Dec 2003 (Box 16, Folder 77)
    - Ken Calls Jerry Shepard. 26 Nov 2003 (Box 16, Folder 78)
    - Meeting with Richard Gibbs (HGC). 6 Aug 2004 (Box 16, Folder 79)
    - Meeting with George Weinstock of BCM to discuss RFP from NLM. 16 Aug 2004 (Box 16, Folder 80)
    - UTMB Entelos Meeting. 1 Dec 2004 (Box 16, Folder 81)
- Series II: Committees, 1986-2007 (Boxes 17-39)
  - Subseries A: Rice University, 1986-2007
    - Rice University Campaign for Computational Engineering's Leadership Committee Handbook (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Rice University Computational Engineering Campaign and Texas Instruments 1995 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Rice University Computer Science Technical Report. 20 Jan 1986 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Graduate Student Admissons 2006 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - CS Graduate Recruits 2006 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Computer Science Faculty Meetings (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Rice: The Next Century. Report of the Strategic Planning Committee (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Classes - Abscences (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Rice Undergraduate Major Surveys (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Undergraduate Surveys and Results (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Strategic Planning Committee (1 of 3) (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Strategic Planning Committee (2 of 3) (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Strategic Planning Committee (3 of 3) (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - George R. Brown School of Engineering Advisory Council (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Rice University - Texas Instruments Collaboration 1998 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - School of Engineering Planning and Research (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Computer Science Research Papers (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Computational Engineering Campaign (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Campaign for Computational Engineering Leadership Committee Handbook (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Neil Binford. 10 May 1996 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Budget Request Adjustment (Building) (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - CEB Parking (Gillis) (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Building - Computer Engineering (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Space 1996 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - CEB Furniture (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Building - Thank You Notes (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Building (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Confidential (building funding) (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Fundraising 4 Oct 1993 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - CE Building Groundbreaking. 4 Nov 1994 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Kresge Foundation (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Computer Engineering Building Fund Donors/Progress (1 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Computer Engineering Building Fund Donors/Progress (2 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Citi Building Meeting. 11 Dec 1992 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Building Fund Prospects (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Keith Cooper Space (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Space Wars CE Lab Building (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Space War Treaty of HB (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Space Issues. 22 March 1991 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Annual Report of Biosciences and Bioengineering 2000 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - "The Architecture of Time" by John Outram. 15 March 1998 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Building Meeting. 23 July 1993 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - CITI Building (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Building Fund (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Computational Science Building (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - New Building Meeting. 31 Aug 1992 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - The New Building. 21 March 1993 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Meeting with Gorry (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Provost Lane (Space). 3 March 1992 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Computational Engineering Campaign Prospects, Schedule (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Citi Building Meeting. 27 May 1993 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - CITI Building (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Engineering Centers (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - General (Faculty) (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Engineering Strategic Planning Committee. 5 June 1996 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Computer Engineering Collaborations/Projects (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Copyright of Courseware (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Microsoft Proposal Teleconference (Tony Hey) (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Citi Distinguished Speaker David Tennenhouse. 29 Sept 2004 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Richard Greeley Resume August 2003 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - GNEP Teleconference. 6 June 2006 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - HPCS AG Meetings (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - NCBC Rice Planning Meeting (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - BioHouston Task Force (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Fundraising (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - February 19 Renaissance (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Italian Renaissance Rice. 19 Feb 1994 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Rice Ad Hoc Security Review Committee as of 1994 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - SEMATECH 2006 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - IT Lecture Series 2003 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Meeting with Garrett Dolan. 23 Oct 2006 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous news articles, problem solutions, research papers (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - CITI-RTC Collaboration (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Computing and Multimedia Services IT Division Fall 1997 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Rice in India and UH Adjunct Faculty Form (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - John Doerr Distinguished Alum Nomination (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - A Five Year Strategic Plan for Information Services and Computing Facilities at Rice University (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Engineering Meeting. 23 April 1997 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Engineering Strategic Planning Committee (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Draft Report by the Ad Hoc Committee on Departmental Structure (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Engineering Strategic Planning Committee Document Drafts (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Engineering Strategic Plan - Drafts. 12 July 1998 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Engineering Strategic Plan - Final. 18 Aug 1998 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Personal Schedule and Workshop Schedule. June 1998 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - NSF Science and Technology Research Centers (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Donations: Tony Gorry/Harvard Hill (Houston Partners/First City Bank) (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Research Administration - A Call to Action (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Engineering Meeting. 14 May 1997 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Engineering Strategic Planning Committee - Final Plan. 18 Aug 1991 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Building Letters (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - President's Luncheon (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Rice IT Advisory Council (ITAC) 2004 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - ITAC Communications Subcommittee (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - ITAC Subgroups 2005 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - ITAC Meeting 28 Feb 2005 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Network Replacement Project. 24 Nov 2004 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Meeting with Ken Kennedy. 22 Nov 2004 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - IT Staff Interviews (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Draft IP Policy March 2004 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - IT Security Officer Telephone Interview (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Software Best Practices for the National Lab Environment (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - IT Subcommittee Meeting. 24 March 2005 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - IT Advisory Committee. 1 Nov 2004 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - ITAC Meeting. 11 April 2005 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - ITAC. January - April 2005 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Rice Committee on Export Control 2003 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Dr. George Rupp (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - K-8 Application Evaluation (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Principal Search (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - K-8 Search Committee (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - Evaluation Forms (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - The Rice School/La Escuela Rice (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - The Rice School Surveys and Responses (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - The Rice School Strategic Planning Workshop (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - The Rice School (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - The Rice School K-9 Proposal and Report 1997 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - K-8 Meeting - Provost Auston (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - K-8 Meeting and Cmt. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - K-8 Meetings (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - K-8 Meeting 3 Sept 1997 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - K-8 Meeting 5 June 1997 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Faculty views on graduate student diversity 2003 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - President's Report (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Malcolm Gillis' Royal Society of Edinburgh Speech. 10 Sept 2001 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Rice Information Structure (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Executive Briefings (Gillis/Rice) (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Faculty Report (Rice/CSD/CRPC) (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Konisky Survey (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - K-8 Memo to Gillis (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Briefing Dr. Gillis re: Bioterrorism Meeting with Senator Hutchinson (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Preparation of Dr. Gillis for Briefing on BioTerror. 22 April 2002 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Rice Alliance "100" Event. 25 July 2002 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Ten most important discoveries at Rice in the past 50 years (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Rice Centers and Institute 2004 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Leebron Inauguration. 1-2 Oct 2004 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Rice BOD Meeting. (IT Presentation). 15 Dec 2004 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Academic Affairs Committee Board of Trustees Mtg. 15 Dec 2004 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Rice Board Mtg. 31 March 2005 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Mtg. with Governor's Higher Education Advisor. 23 Feb 2006 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Alumni Leadership Conference. 20 Sept. 2002 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Woodhill Strategy 2002 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Fundraising Contacts re: John Cocke, named Chair at Duke University 2003 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Micron Campus Visit 25 July 2003 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Tapia/Doerr/Kamen (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Development - Rice U. Prospect Selectees by Prof. Ken Kennedy (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Poduska Proposal 18 Oct 2004 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - CITI Development Prospects 2003 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Development Trip to the Bay Area (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Rice Associates' Dinner. 3 Feb 2004 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - NI/Trouchard Foundation Planning Mtg. 16 Feb 2004 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Development Training Sessions (Kennedy) 2003 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - AMD Donation 22 May 2003 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Dan Marcek (HP) Visit. 17 Feb 2005 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Call Behnaam Aazhang re: TI/Development call report 2004 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - John Doerr Proposal (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Misc. Development Info and Correspondence call reports (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Kennedy Conference Room Naming Event 2006 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - IT Security and Access Subcommittee (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Rice Security Committee (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Rice Research Council 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - IT Support at Rice Committee (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Rice Committee on IT Security and Access - Final Report 2002 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - IBM Presentation. 10 June 2004 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - Baker Institute A/V Meeting. 17 March 2005 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Baker Institute A/V Meeting. 13 May 2005 (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Rice-draft-Copyright Policy (for review) (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - IT Advisory Committee 2004 (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Network IT Meeting (Executive Summary) (Box 19, Folder 55)
    - Ronnie Wells (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - Update on Advisory Committee PR (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - Information Technology Advisory Committee. 30 Nov 2006 (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - Rice Master Planning Meetings 2003 (Box 19, Folder 59)
    - Rice Research Council (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - S and E Shared Computing Committee 2003 (Box 19, Folder 61)
    - Rice Research Council 2003 (Box 19, Folder 62)
    - Committee on Export Controls (Box 19, Folder 63)
    - IT Security Committee 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 64)
    - Rice Institute of Biosciences and Bioengineering (2005) (Box 19, Folder 65)
    - iRice Materials - Campaign 2001 (Box 19, Folder 66)
    - Computer Science Committee on the Digital Env. 2001 (Box 19, Folder 67)
    - Rice MHs (Box 19, Folder 68)
    - Information Technology Advisory Committee. Oct 2005-Sept 2006 (Box 19, Folder 69)
    - Engineering Planning (Box 19, Folder 70)
    - Engineering Planning Survey (Box 19, Folder 71)
    - IT Network Project (Box 19, Folder 72)
    - Research Council Mtg. 21 Oct 1998 (Box 19, Folder 73)
    - Rice Alliance Innovation Concept Forum. 22 Jan 2000 (Box 19, Folder 74)
    - Letter from Malcolm Gillis re: DoD Award (Box 19, Folder 75)
    - Institute Directors BioSci Lunch Meetings (Box 19, Folder 76)
    - Education/Outreach - CGrADS Robotics Mtg. 10 Sept 2001 (Box 19, Folder 77)
    - Mtg with FIRST re: GirlTECH. 28 Aug 2001 (Box 19, Folder 78)
    - FIRST Education/Outreach (Robotics) (Box 19, Folder 79)
    - Mtg. to Discuss FIRST. 30 Nov 2001 (Box 19, Folder 80)
    - Teleconference with FIRST. 1 Nov 2001 (Box 19, Folder 81)
    - CRC Planning - 2005 (Box 19, Folder 82)
    - Strategic Partnership Information April 2005 (Box 19, Folder 83)
    - Dan Updegrove's Visit. 2 June 2004 (Box 19, Folder 84)
    - Tour of MDACC Proton Therapy Center. 23 March 2005 (Box 19, Folder 85)
    - CRC Mtg. with Dr. Levy. 3 March 2005 (Box 19, Folder 86)
    - GRB Space Planning Committee 2005 (Box 19, Folder 87)
    - GRB Strategic Plan 1998 (Box 19, Folder 88)
    - Staff Ranking 2007 (Box 19, Folder 89)
    - GRB Current and Future Space Needs. April 2006 (Box 19, Folder 90)
    - NSF/MSP Aldine ISD Math and Science Grant Proposal - Letter of Commitment. December 2002 (Box 19, Folder 91)
    - Charter Day Subcommittee Mtg. 9 Jan 1989 (Box 19, Folder 92)
    - Community Subcommittee - Rice Charter Day (Box 19, Folder 93)
    - Agreement - Computing Facilities (Box 19, Folder 94)
    - Centennial Committee 1988 (Box 19, Folder 95)
    - Accreditation - Computer Sciences Accred. Board 1986 (Box 19, Folder 96)
    - Chairs and Institute Director Meetings (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - ITAC Meetings (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Security Report (Draft) (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - ITAC Meeting Schedule 2007 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - IT Working Group for Strategic Planning 2006 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Institute for Global Health Technologies; Strategic Planning Update Mtg. 2006 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - A Vision of Energy in the 21st Century; Excerpt from Strategic Plan; Translational Biomedical Engineering Partnership (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Engineering Research Expenditures 2000-2006 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Misc. Rice Projects (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Interim Report on School of Engineering, Oct. 2006 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - ASC PSAAP 2006 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Health Strategic Planning Committee (2006) (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Faculty Recruiting Committee (2006/2007) (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - President's Office; Rice and India 2006 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Dean of Engineering Strategic Planning (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - ITWG Meetings (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - TAPIA 2003 Conference (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Faculty Meetings 2003 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Accreditation (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - SACS Accreditation, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Accreditation - Opponents (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Letters, notes (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Kennedy (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Dean of Engineering Search Committee 2004 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Final Dean Search MHs (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Dean Search (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Associate Provost Search (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Research Faculty (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Research Council Notes Sept 1987 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Research Council Summary Notes Oct 1987 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Research Council - In. Draft March 1988 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Advisory Council - Five Year Plan 1988 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Advisory Council Minutes/Agenda Oct 1986 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Advisory Council- E and CE Report Oct 1987 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Advisory Council Minutes May 1988 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Advisory Council Minutes April 1988 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Advisory Committee, 10 Nov. 1988 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Advisory Council - Spring 1992 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Advisory Council Nov 1990 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Town Meeting - Shepherd School Rehearsal Hall. 7 Dec (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Comp. Plan Board. 22 Nov. 1988 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Comp. Planning Board Report. Spring 1988 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Houston Supercomputer (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Computer Planning Board Implementation Overview (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Computer Planning Board Subcommittee Report (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Site Visit (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Computer Planning Board (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Plans - 15 Feb 1988 (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Computer Planning Board Summary Report May 1989 (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Computer Planning Board/Committee (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - Owlnet (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - Summary Report - Jan 1988 (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Self Study Visiting Committee Report (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - Networking (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - Reunion Giving Campaign 1997-98 (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - Alumni College Talk - Next Generation Internet. 16 April 1999 (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - Alumni Office (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - "A Five-Year Strategic Plan for Information Services and Computing Facilities at Rice University" (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Subseries B: Non-Rice, 1987-2007
    - Planning to Deal with Export-Controlled and Proprietary Programs and Data (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Bioengineering (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Software for HPC Architecture Slides (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - ARPA (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - OTA Commercialization (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - PITAC (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - ICASE Notes (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - HPC Toolkit (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences - Nominations 2006 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - HPC Teleconference. 7 Nov 2005 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - U.S. News World Report Best Graduate Schools 2003 Edition (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Review - due August 20, 2004 - The Future of Supercomputing (report) (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Rice Meetings - Collaborative Research Symposium 2006 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Mtg. to Review and Discuss the CITI Report (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Biomedical Information Science and Technology Institute (BISTI) Jan 2003 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Mtg. with David Dill (CITI lecturer) 2004 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - IT Issues Meeting (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Eman Group Mtg. 4 Aug 2003 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Ken's Keck Seminar. 25 April 2003 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Mtg. with Dr. Levy re: Grid funding and SFITL. 30 June 2004 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Network Architecture and Design Presentation 2004 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - NCBC Planning Meeting. 28 May 2004 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Mtg. with Dr. Wah Chiu re: NCBC. 9 July 2004 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - PPoPP 1997 (papers) (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Research Council Meeting. 16 Dec 1998 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Livermore Consulting (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Livermore Claim Forms (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Livermore Access Card (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Consulting Forms - Lawrence Livermore Laboratories (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Livermore General Info (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Livermore Consulting Agreement (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - VSM Agreement (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - LASL - McKnight Report (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Consulting Agreement. 15 April 1993 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Los Alamos Consultant Agreement (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Los Alamos Collaborator Agreement (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Los Alamos Consulting (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - LANL (General) (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Security booklet (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - LANL "Q" Clearance 2002 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Ken Kennedy Fingerprint Cards (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Los Alamos Security (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - IDA (Consulting) (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - IBM Site Visits (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - E-Systems Corp (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - NAE (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Houston Partners/NMVP Lovell vs. WhizBang Settlement Agreement. 18 Feb 2002 (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - Houston Partners - Lovell vs. WhizBang 2002 (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - NMVP/Houston Partners Conference Call re: Dennis Bayes. 28 Jan 2002 (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - Houston Partners - NMVP Asset Purchase Agreement 2002 (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - Houston Partners/NMVP - unaudited/unconsolidated F/S 2001 (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - Houston Partners - NMVP Financial Statements. Jan 2000 - Sept 2001 (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - Houston Partners - NMVP/Crescent Moon Settlement Agreement 2001 (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - Houston Partners - NMVP Overview of CY 2001 (Box 21, Folder 54)
    - Houston Partners - NMVP 2001 Board of Directors Meeting (Box 21, Folder 55)
    - Houston Partners Board of Advisors (Box 21, Folder 56)
    - New Media Venture Partners, Inc. (Box 21, Folder 57)
    - TeleSuite (Box 21, Folder 58)
    - Houston Venture Partnres, Ltd. Portfolio Valuation Committee and Board of Advisors Meeting. 4 May 2000 (Box 21, Folder 59)
    - Houston Partners (Box 21, Folder 60)
    - Access Ware (Box 21, Folder 61)